# Wesley Maffly-Kipp

Web Developer | Musician 919-259-4410

wesleymafflykipp@gmail.com https://www.wesmk.com/ https://github.com/maffkipp

# **Profile**

I am a full stack web developer with a flair for creativity and outside-of-the-box problem solving. My experience as a musician has given me the ability to perform well under pressure and improvise when the situation calls for it, skills I put to use building powerful, elegant web apps.

#### Skills

Front End: HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, Jquery, React.js, Redux, SASS, Firebase, Webpack, ES6

Back End: Node.js, Express, MongoDB, Nginx, Python, Flask, OAuth

Other Relevant Skills: Git/Github, React Native

# Web Development Experience

## **General Assembly - Web Development Immersive**

12 week full-time program focused on web development tools and best practices.

#### Pete's Pedals: https://www.petespedals.net/

I built this site for my dad's guitar pedal business using React and the Contentful CMS. I wanted him to be able to determine the site's content without having to navigate the codebase, and I did not want to be tied into the layouts of a more traditional CMS.

## Bogbody Band Website: <a href="https://www.bogbody.band/">https://www.bogbody.band/</a>

This is a website built for one of the bands I play with in Austin. I wanted to make a simple, elegant site that served as a hub for information and media related to the band. I used Webpack as a module bundler, along with Babel and Sass.

See more in my portfolio: <a href="https://www.wesmk.com/">https://www.wesmk.com/</a>

# **Other Work Experience**

#### Fricano's Deli | Shift Lead/Line Cook | September 2013- Current

Family-owned sandwich shop in West Campus. Responsibilities include cooking, taking orders and serving customers, prep work, cleaning, assigning tasks to other employees, opening/closing the store, preparing and delivering catering orders, and ensuring that the business is successful and customers are satisfied.

## Musician | Self-employed | January 2011- Current

I have been playing and performing music for almost my entire life. Over the last seven years in Austin, I have performed frequently with 6 different bands on Bass Guitar, Electric and Acoustic Guitar, Vocals, Banjo, and Keyboards. I have worked on a variety of recording projects as well, working at Fifth Street Studios, Estuary Recording, Ohm Recording Facility, Fire Station Studios in San Marcos, and Nightsound Studios in Chapel Hill, NC.

#### Education

12-week Web Development Immersive Course at General Assembly in Austin, TX, Fall 2017 15 credit hours of Computer Science coursework at Austin Community College, Spring-Fall 2015 60 credit hours of Physics coursework at UT Austin, Winter 2011-Spring 2013